Colleges, right? I don't give a fuck about that shit. I've never went to college. Why would I care?
Why should I give a fuck about the college? There's not genocide at the college. I give a fuck about
what's going on on the other side of the world, but why would I give a fuck about the college?
Because Africa is working at the college? Shut the fuck up. This is shit I'm talking about.
Stupid motherfuckers at the college. We were under attack. 11 terrorists blew our shit up. 3,000
people dead. What the fuck did we do, America? Do y'all remember what we did? If you're from the
1900s, you remember. I'm not sure what's going on with sis, but if you want to come to a comedy show
where we do care about college and college students and folks who didn't go to college and
black liberation and Palestine and Africa and the Sudan and Congo and, you know, things that
matter. If you want all of that, plus a show where you might hear about drug dealer dick,
titty pics, savages, hear nigga damn laws, Juneteenth, funny style interviewers. You want to find out what
a cotton tickle is and more? Well, then maybe come to an Amanda Seals show, all right? Because we're
going to talk about all of that and have a good ass time doing it. You'll also find out when my braids
look like this. Link in bio or go to amandaseals.com for the Unlikable tour. See you there.